Good Exploratorium! Nice explorers!
Yay!
I'm Ikaru Suzuki and Hinano Sakura!
Please give them my best regards!
Nice to meet you! We are the "Iinei-Exploratorium"!
So today, we'll be at the Nakayoshi Convenience Store.
What are you going to explore?
Oh!
Oh, no!
Let me introduce you to the multipurpose free space, Culture Blizzard!
Wow!
Located on the 4th floor, Culture Blizzard is a multi-purpose space, but did you know? Do you know what it is?
It's located in the back of the building on the 4th floor, and today we're going to take a look at what it can be used for.
Let's get moving! Let's go!
Here we are! Mr. Curren$y Purikura card!
If you go through the Purikura Street this time, you'll arrive here.
Let's open the forbidden door and take a look inside.
Open! The door of dreams!
New entry!
New entry successful!
Don't tell me to do something bad!
What do you think? I've been inside.
I can give you a lesson!
Look! There's a mirror!
Look!
After all
The most exciting thing for us is
The number of air conditioners!
Air conditioners?
There are always more!
There are so many! Air conditioners!
Yes! For our lessons.
It's great!
The days get pretty hot in the summer.
Shouldn't we switch to this one?
Yeah, it's nice.
It's nice.
I don't care about that.
I'd like to give you a lesson.
I'm not really here for an inside view of the school.
But it's just the right size.
It looks like it could be used for a variety of things.
I'd like to ask the staff what we can actually do here.
I'd like to ask the staff what we can actually do here?
Yes.
The manager, Mr. Hayazawa, is here.
Pleased to meet you.
He's cute.
How did you get so close so quickly?
It's the first time I've been called on the spot.
First time.
Let's ask a few questions.
Ask questions, both of you.
All right.
What can we do here?
Well, first of all...
Well, as you both mentioned at the beginning.
As you said at the beginning, we have mirrors, so the main thing is to have a place for dance and performance artists to practice.
A place for dance and performance artists to practice.
And if you think about it without the mirrors...
This space can be used for
Mini events
If you have an event with less than 30 people, you can
can be held in this space.
And if you want to have an event in such a case, you can set up a stage
We can also set up a stage about 17 centimeters high.
I see.
We can build a small stage.
You can also use it for events where you can put down mats or something on the floor.
It can also be used for events.
If it is something that makes use of this space
The only thing you can't do is eat things.
The only thing you can't do is eat.
Other than that, I don't think there's anything else that you can't do.
And then there's the firearms principle.
We're going to have events and things like that.
I'd like to use a smoke machine
I'd like to clean up the structure.
But if we do that, we'll get kicked out by the postal service.
I'm sorry, but I can't do anything that would emit smoke.
Smoke machine
Smoke machines...
We're also not allowed to have food.
If there is anything else that you think we can do, please let us know.
What is it?
If you would like to discuss it, please contact us.
As for stopping, well, I think that the Eagle will probably pinch us at 8 o'clock at night,
I can take a nap until 8:00.
Take a nap!
We already have a yoga mat for you to use in the luxury of your reservation,
You can pull it out and sleep from 10:00 to 8:00 with 5 people in the room.
Mr. Hino, you don't want us to oversleep, right? Or in case of an event.
If you stay here, you won't be late if you don't oversleep.
Or the first sale, for example.
The first sale.
There was a time when you were not here for the opening.
Wow!
Oh?
You got married here.
You can go to the wedding.
Just no candlelight service.
Ah...
Yes, you can. It's a dibble.
Wow!
Do you have live performances here?
Maybe a mini live show with an audience?
Do you have any mini live performances?
We usually hold live events twice a month, sometimes three times a month.
Live events are held about three times a month.
Wow!
I see.
By the way, today is...
Can I do a live concert now?
Now? Now?
I'll give you special permission!
Oh, my God!
You can do it!
I know it's short notice, but let's do a guerrilla live show now.
Let's do it!
It'll be a bit lonely without an audience.
I'll announce it on eBeans' X.
"Guinari Expedition Guerrilla Live" will be held here in 30 minutes.
We'll announce that we're going to do a guerrilla live show here in 30 minutes, and only those who can make it will be allowed in.
We'll have the two perform a song.
You never know if they'll show up, because it's the middle of the day on a weekday.
On the other hand, if they came now, what would they do at work?
So we'll make an announcement and have the song performed for those who show up within the 30-minute window.
Okay?
Thank you very much.
Let's announce it on X right away.
Well, we have to announce that we're doing a guerrilla show.
I just borrowed a smartphone from the staff at eBeans.
I'm in the account.
I'm in!
So let's create a tweet!
I'm X!
Post!
No! I'm gonna wear the e-lo mask!
I ain't looking!
Okay, what do we do now?
Today.
I'll see you in half an hour or so.
14:00.
15 minutes.
from
INNARI Sankai
Yeah...
Seirira Live
Wow, too hot!
First call for sure!
Heart
It's done!
Can I ask you to read this?
What are you doing?
In a half an hour, at 2:15 p.m.
At Culture Blizzard on the 4th floor of E-Beans
Iginari Expedition Guerrilla Live will be held!
Heart
Admission free!
I want to
Rumman first concert is waiting for you!
Amp
Kultureb
Ah, but oh well.
Perfect.
It's good, isn't it?
Hey.
Suddenly, I was wondering what happened to your E-Beans account.
You might think I've been hijacked.
I wonder if it'll last.
You believe this, right? You probably believe it, right?
I think so. Whoever believes in it will be saved.
Why are you doing this? How often do you say that?
I was taught. I was taught.
I see.
Okay, well, just send this over.
I'm very excited to see if it comes.
Is it coming? Will it come?
Well, it's time to go.
I'll send it and wait for half an hour.
I'll wait.
Okay.
Posted?
It has been submitted.
Then I'll wait for 30 minutes from here for a guest to arrive.
Let's wait.
I'll wait.
Okay, it's been 15 minutes since I tweeted the announcement.
It's now 2 o'clock, and so far, no customers have arrived yet.
So no one in the health department is coming?
The song will start in 15 minutes. We'll just have to have a little faith.
What do we believe in?
You'll be saved.
Okay, it's 2:15.
It's time to go live.
It's nerve-wracking.
When we open the door, I don't know if the audience will be there or not.
I don't know, but either way, we're going to have a live show.
Can I open the door and take a look?
Okay, please.
Let's see how many are there.
I'll see you there.
Okay, well, I'm gonna open the doors now.
I'd like to open the door.
Let's go.
There's three of them.
No work today?
No, I'm not working.
Thank you, ma'am.
We're going to have a live performance of "Gili-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
We're going to be holding a live concert.
Please come inside.
Oh, thank God.
You made it.
I've never seen anyone like that before.
Thank you for coming to the Eastern Ghastly Concert today.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
Where did you come from?
From here.
I'm from Sendai.
Were you at work?
Home.
You came to my house?
I'm so happy!
By the way, how was the closing?
Do you want to hear about the closing?
From Atchivala.
Acha acha acha.
Excuse me, sir.
Thank you very much.
And the next one.
I'm at work.
I need to see the dentist.
I've got a toothache all of a sudden.
Thank you.
I think it's around here.
Right here, right here.
I guess you're at work.
Oh, thank God.
Can I ask you one last question?
May I?
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
It's true.
More.
Wait.
I'm late.
Late, late.
Are you at work?
Yes, I am.
Thank you.
So there's four of us now.
I didn't have any fans.
They're coming.
Another one's coming.
Thank you. Thank you.
Where did you come from today?
I left work today from Sendai.
That's great.
I lie on my face.
By the way, I closed with
Fanfare!
Goo!
re.
I followed you on Twitter for the first time.
Nice to meet you.
I didn't know you're a 1Gen.
Yeah, I'm glad to hear it!
Thank you all, 9 players.
Almost pre-cure.
Oh, pre-cure.
You look radiant
Thank you.
Okay, everyone.
We're going live now.
Let's get excited!
Yeah!
It's great. It's okay.
Listen to this.
Please follow us!
Eggs Are Not Alive Tohoku Stars
We are not alive Northeast Stars
Shape up differently so he's my light
Beyond the stars, the curtain now opens
Egg is not alive, Tohoku Stars
Now we are not alive, Tohoku Stars
Hoshi ha gazes at me, I'll be back tomorrow
Until the stars fall, the light shines
If it's about you, it's about me
Someday, I'll be with someone.
Hikaru, hikaru, hikaru, hikaru, hikaru, hikaru, hikaru.
We can't do it! We can't lose!
We'll fight, fight, fight, grab it and keep the rhythm up
Even if we fall a million times, we won't give up
Egg is not alive, Tohoku Stars
We are not alive, Tohoku Stars
If I could turn on the lights, I'd turn on the stars
If it's light out, I want to give you a star
If I believe in what I've been trying so hard to do
Someday, someday, someday, your wish will turn into two birds with one stone
If I'm dealt with only by love, I'll be rocking and someday
I'll think of it, and when the breath comes out, I'll burst into tears
While you're waiting for me, seriously, I can't get out of it
I believe in a heart that's not there, that's shining brightly
I won't give up on any regrets, any happiness.
Let's do it! Space, space, space
Thank you very much.
What a blast!
That was a lot of fun.
Well, then, sadly...
This is the last one for today.
Ehhhh...
Um...
That's not what we're doing.
Well, thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
I know it was short.
But it was a lot of fun.
That's all.
This is Stardust from With Knuckle
Rinari and Ofuden.
Thank you very much!
Quietly, quietly, stop clapping
Please go home.
Go home, go home.
Thank you.
It's not a fake.
Go home.
Go back to work.
It's a weekday afternoon.
Thanks, man.
I'll send a video to the office with your face on it.
Go home, go home.
There you go again.
Go home.
Next time it'll cost you more.
Thank you very much.
Good luck at work.
Bye-bye.
Don't dwell on it.
Go home. Gaynar Live is over!
How was it?
Strange feelings!
Indeed!
What happened?
Back gundam!
Isn't it amazing?
I was dreaming!
I honestly thought you might not come!
I was afraid you wouldn't show up, time-wise and day-wise.
You came a lot.
How many?
Six!
And for the first time!
It was the first time!
We had a 3D!
First time!
What a memory!
Legendary!
I hope it continues from here!
Because it's that deep!
They come from everywhere.
Isn't this what it's all about?
Maybe we should turn the guerrilla gigs into regular gigs.
That might be a good idea.
It was fun.
Was it fun?
It's good once in a while.
It's kind of exciting, isn't it?
I'd be so happy if you came.
I understand. Now you know.
The gratitude of the customers.
It's a good plan.
The plan is changing.
LOL.
Remember the pictures.
I'll just say that I enjoyed the live show.
Thank you both for your hard work.
Thank you.
Thank you also to those who came.
Thank you for coming. So, today
I'll be at Culture Blizzard.
We had a guerrilla live performance
Thank you very much for your kindness.
Thank you very much, manager.
Thank you very much for answering our urgent request.
I am very grateful for your help.
We will be holding a lot of events including this guerrilla live performance.
Mini events
sales, etc.
We can use it for a wide variety of things.
How do you make reservations?
Reservations can be made
Please visit Edinz's website
Culture Blizzard's
There is a link to the Culture Blizzard page on Edinz's website.
You can make a reservation from there.
The price is 3 hours per slot.
Weekdays: 4,000 yen
Weekends and holidays are 6,000 yen
Very economical!
Weekday morning slot
from 10:00 to 1:00
3 hours
You can use it as many times as you want in a month.
tickets can be used as many times as you like in a month.
can be sold for 12,000 yen.
Very inexpensive
We are offering this service at a very reasonable price.
We are looking forward to seeing you.
We hope you all will join us.
Mr. Culture Blizzard
Please buy it.
Best regards.
Bye bye!